<resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
  <string name="intro_benefit_headline">[Möŕé öþéñ îñţéŕñéţ åççéšš one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="intro_benefit_body">[Îñţŕå þŕöţéçţš ýöû ƒŕöm ÐÑŠ måñîþûļåţîöñ, å çýбéŕ åţţåçķ ûšéð ţö бļöçķ åççéšš ţö ñéŵš šîţéš, šöçîåļ méðîå þļåţƒöŕmš åñð méššåĝîñĝ åþþš.\ñ\ñŴĥîļé Îñţŕå þŕöţéçţš ýöû åĝåîñšţ ÐÑŠ måñîþûļåţîöñ, ţĥéŕé åŕé öţĥéŕ, möŕé çömþļîçåţéð бļöçķîñĝ ţéçĥñîqûéš åñð åţţåçķš ţĥåţ Îñţŕå ðöéšñ\'ţ þŕöţéçţ åĝåîñšţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour thirtyfive]</string>
  <string name="intro_manipulation_headline">[Þŕöţéçţîöñ ƒŕöm ÐÑŠ måñîþûļåţîöñ one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="intro_manipulation_body">[Îñţŕå þŕöţéçţš ýöûŕ çöññéçţîöñ ţö ţĥé Ðömåîñ Ñåmé Šýšţém (ÐÑŠ), ŵĥîçĥ þŕövîðéš ţĥé éxåçţ åððŕéššéš ýöû ñééð ţö vîšîţ å ŵéбšîţé öŕ öþéñ åñ åþþ.\ñ\ñÎñţŕå ûšéš éñçŕýþţîöñ ţö éñšûŕé ţĥåţ ŕéšûļţš çåñ\’ţ бé måñîþûļåţéð, ĥéļþîñĝ ýöû šåƒéļý åççéšš ţĥé îñţéŕñéţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo]</string>
  <string name="intro_details_headline">[Öñé ļåšţ ţĥîñĝ… one two]</string>
  <string name="intro_details_body">[Ţåþ ÖĶ ţö åļļöŵ Îñţŕå ţö þŕöţéçţ ýöûŕ ÐÑŠ ŕéqûéšţš. Бý ðéƒåûļţ, ţĥéý ŵîļļ бé ŕöûţéð ţö Ĝööĝļé Þûбļîç ÐÑŠ (ᐅ<a href="https://developers.google.com/speed/public-dns/privacy">ᐊÞŕîvåçý Þöļîçýᐅ</a>ᐊ). Ýöû çåñ çĥööšé åñöţĥéŕ šéŕvîçé îñ ţĥé åþþ šéţţîñĝš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive]</string>
  <string name="intro_back">[бåçķ one]</string>
  <string name="intro_next">[ñéxţ one]</string>
  <string name="intro_accept">[åççéþţ one]</string>
  <string name="drawer_open">[Öþéñ ñåvîĝåţîöñ ðŕåŵéŕ one two three]</string>
  <string name="drawer_close">[Çļöšé ñåvîĝåţîöñ ðŕåŵéŕ one two three]</string>
  <string name="home">[Ĥömé one]</string>
  <string name="settings">[Šéţţîñĝš one]</string>
  <string name="support">[Šûþþöŕţ one]</string>
  <string name="privacy_link">[Þŕîvåçý Þöļîçý one two]</string>
  <string name="tos_link">[Ţéŕmš öƒ Šéŕvîçé one two]</string>
  <string name="source_code">[Šöûŕçé Çöðé one two]</string>
  <string name="credits_text">[Îñţŕå ŵåš måðé бý ᐅ<a href="https://jigsaw.google.com">ᐊĴîĝšåŵᐅ</a>ᐊ. ÎÞ ļöçåţîöñš åŕé бåšéð öñ ðåţå
    ƒŕöm ÐБ-ÎÞ.çöm. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
  <string name="indicator_on">[Öñ one]</string>
  <string name="indicator_off">[Öƒƒ one]</string>
  <string name="status_exposed">[Éxþöšéð one]</string>
  <string name="explanation_exposed">[Ýöûŕ çöññéçţîöñ îš éxþöšéð ţö ÐÑŠ åţţåçķš. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
  <string name="status_protected">[Þŕöţéçţéð one two]</string>
  <string name="explanation_protected">[Ýöûŕ çöññéçţîöñ îš þŕöţéçţéð ƒŕöm ÐÑŠ åţţåçķš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
  <string name="status_upgraded">[Vûļñéŕåбļé one two]</string>
  <string name="explanation_upgraded">[Ýöûŕ çöññéçţîöñ îš çûŕŕéñţļý þŕöţéçţéð бý Åñðŕöîð Þŕîvåţé ÐÑŠ, бûţ åñ åţţåçķéŕ çöûļð ðîšåбļé
    öŕ ûñðéŕmîñé ţĥîš þŕöţéçţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty]</string>
  <string name="status_strict">[Þŕöţéçţéð бý Åñðŕöîð one two three]</string>
  <string name="explanation_strict">[Îñţŕå ĥåš ðéţéçţéð ţĥåţ ţĥé Åñðŕöîð Þŕîvåţé ÐÑŠ šéţţîñĝ îš éñåбļéð.  Ţĥîš méåñš ýöûŕ ÐÑŠ
    qûéŕîéš åŕé åļŕéåðý þŕöţéçţéð, šö ţĥéŕé\'š ñö ñééð ţö éñåбļé Îñţŕå. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree]</string>
  <string name="status_starting">[Šţåŕţîñĝ… one two]</string>
  <string name="explanation_starting">[Ĥåñĝ ţîĝĥţ.  Îñţŕå îš éšţåбļîšĥîñĝ å šéŕvéŕ çöññéçţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
  <string name="status_waiting">[Ŵåîţîñĝ… one]</string>
  <string name="explanation_offline">[Ýöûŕ ðévîçé îš öƒƒļîñé.  Îñţŕå îš ŵåîţîñĝ ƒöŕ å ñéţŵöŕķ çöññéçţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
  <string name="explanation_vpn">[Îñţŕå ĥåš ðéţéçţéð åñöţĥéŕ VÞÑ öñ ýöûŕ ðévîçé.  Îƒ ýöû éñåбļé Îñţŕå, ţĥåţ VÞÑ ŵîļļ бé ðîšåбļéð.
    Îñţŕå îš ñöţ åš šéçûŕé åš å ţŕûšţéð VÞÑ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone]</string>
  <string name="explanation_failing">[Ŵåŕñîñĝ: Qûéŕîéš åŕé ƒåîļîñĝ.  Ýöû måý ŵåñţ ţö çĥööšé å ðîƒƒéŕéñţ šéŕvéŕ åñð ŕéšţåŕţ Îñţŕå. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]</string>
  <string name="system_details">[Šýšţém ðéţåîļš one two]</string>
  <string name="num_requests">[Ļîƒéţîmé qûéŕîéš one two]</string>
  <string name="num_requests_headline">[ÐÑŠ qûéŕîéš ĥåþþéñ ŵĥéñ ýöûŕ ðévîçé ļööķš ûþ ţĥé ÎÞ åððŕéšš ƒöŕ å ðömåîñ ñåmé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
  <string name="num_requests_body">[Ţĥîš våļûé šĥöŵš ţĥé ţöţåļ ñûmбéŕ öƒ ÐÑŠ qûéŕîéš ţĥåţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé ĥåš þéŕƒöŕméð ŵĥîļé Îñţŕå ŵåš
    åçţîvé.  Îñţŕå éñçŕýþţš ţĥéšé qûéŕîéš åñð šéñðš ţĥém ţö å ţŕûšţéð šéŕvéŕ ţö måķé šûŕé ýöû\'ŕé
    ĝéţţîñĝ åûţĥéñţîç ŕéšûļţš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine]</string>
  <string name="queries_per_minute">[Ŕéçéñţ qûéŕîéš one two]</string>
  <string name="queries_per_minute_headline">[ÐÑŠ qûéŕîéš ĥåþþéñ åţ ţĥé бéĝîññîñĝ öƒ éåçĥ çöññéçţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
  <string name="queries_per_minute_body">[Ţĥîš våļûé šĥöŵš ţĥé ñûmбéŕ öƒ ÐÑŠ qûéŕîéš ţĥåţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé ĥåš þéŕƒöŕméð îñ ţĥé ļåšţ mîñûţé.
    Ļöåðîñĝ å çömþļéx ŵéбþåĝé çåñ ŕéqûîŕé övéŕ å ĥûñðŕéð ÐÑŠ qûéŕîéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree]</string>
  <string name="transport_label">[Éñçŕýþţéð ţŕåñšþöŕţ one two three]</string>
  <string name="transport_headline">[Éñçŕýþţîöñ þŕöţéçţš ýöûŕ qûéŕîéš ƒŕöm þŕýîñĝ éýéš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
  <string name="transport_body">[Ŵĥéñ ýöû ûšé Îñţŕå, ýöûŕ ÐÑŠ qûéŕîéš åŕé éñçŕýþţéð, šö ţĥåţ öñļý ýöû åñð ýöûŕ ÐÑŠ šéŕvéŕ çåñ šéé
    ŵĥåţ ÐÑŠ qûéŕîéš ýöû åŕé måķîñĝ.  Îñţŕå îmþļéméñţš ţĥé ÐÑŠ övéŕ ĤŢŢÞŠ þŕöţöçöļ ƒöŕ éñçŕýþţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix]</string>
  <string name="default_transport_label">[Ðéƒåûļţ ţŕåñšþöŕţ one two three]</string>
  <string name="insecure_transport">[ûñéñçŕýþţéð one two]</string>
  <string name="insecure_transport_headline">[Бåšîç ÐÑŠ îš ûñéñçŕýþţéð one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="insecure_transport_body">[Möšţ ðévîçéš åñð ñéţŵöŕķš ûšé бåšîç ÐÑŠ, ŵĥîçĥ îš ûñéñçŕýþţéð, šö ýöûŕ ÐÑŠ qûéŕîéš çöûļð бé
    öбšéŕvéð öŕ möðîƒîéð бý åñýöñé öñ ţĥé ñéţŵöŕķ.  Šömé ñéŵ ðévîçéš šûþþöŕţ ÐÑŠ övéŕ ŢĻŠ, ŵĥîçĥ
    éñçŕýþţš ýöûŕ qûéŕîéš бûţ çåñ\'ţ þŕöţéçţ ýöû îƒ ţĥé šéŕvéŕ îš måļîçîöûš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree]</string>
  <string name="server_label">[Šéçûŕé ÐÑŠ šéŕvéŕ one two three]</string>
  <string name="server_headline">[Ýöû ðéšéŕvé ţö ûšé å ţŕûšţŵöŕţĥý ÐÑŠ šéŕvéŕ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
  <string name="server_body">[Ţĥîš ƒîéļð šĥöŵš ţĥé ñåmé öƒ ţĥé šéçûŕé ÐÑŠ šéŕvéŕ ţĥåţ ýöû\'ŕé ûšîñĝ.  Ýöû çåñ åļšö çĥåñĝé ţö å
    ðîƒƒéŕéñţ šéŕvéŕ îñ ţĥé Šéţţîñĝš méñû. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone]</string>
  <string name="default_server_label">[Çûŕŕéñţ ÐÑŠ šéŕvéŕ one two three]</string>
  <string name="insecure_server_headline">[Ýöû çåñ çĥööšé ýöûŕ öŵñ ÐÑŠ šéŕvéŕ one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="insecure_server_body">[Ŵĥéñ Îñţŕå îš ðîšåбļéð, möšţ ðévîçéš åŕé þŕé-çöñƒîĝûŕéð ţö ûšé ţĥé ÐÑŠ šéŕvéŕ ýöûŕ ñéţŵöŕķ
    öþéŕåţöŕ þîçķš. Ţĥîš ƒîéļð šĥöŵš ţĥé ÎÞ åððŕéšš öƒ ţĥé ÐÑŠ šéŕvéŕ ţĥåţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé îš çûŕŕéñţļý
    ûšîñĝ. Ŵîţĥ Îñţŕå öŕ Åñðŕöîð Þ, ýöû çåñ éåšîļý šéļéçţ å šéŕvéŕ öƒ ýöûŕ çĥöîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour]</string>
  <string name="strict_mode_server_headline">[Ýöû\'vé šéļéçţéð å šéçûŕé šéŕvéŕ one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="strict_mode_server_body">[Ţĥîš ƒîéļð šĥöŵš ţĥé ñåmé öƒ ţĥé ÐÑŠ šéŕvéŕ ţĥåţ ýöû çöñƒîĝûŕéð îñ Åñðŕöîð\'š Þŕîvåţé ÐÑŠ
    šéţţîñĝ.  Ŵĥéñ Îñţŕå îš ðîšåбļéð, ýöûŕ åþþš šĥöûļð šéñð ÐÑŠ qûéŕîéš ţö ţĥîš šéŕvéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive]</string>
  <string name="unknown_server">[(ûñķñöŵñ šéŕvéŕ) one two]</string>
  <string name="show_history">[Šĥöŵ ŕéçéñţ qûéŕîéš one two three]</string>
  <string name="query_label">[Qûéŕý one]</string>
  <string name="type_label">[Ţýþé one]</string>
  <string name="latency_label">[Ļåţéñçý one]</string>
  <string name="resolver_label">[Ŕéšöļvéŕ ļöçåţîöñ one two three]</string>
  <string name="destination_label">[Ðéšţîñåţîöñ šéŕvéŕ one two three]</string>
  <string name="server_choice">[Šéļéçţ ÐÑŠ övéŕ ĤŢŢÞŠ Šéŕvéŕ one two three four five six]</string>
  <string name="server_choice_summary">[Çûŕŕéñţļý ᐅ%sᐊ one two three]</string>
  <string name="server_choice_custom">[Çûšţöm šéŕvéŕ ÛŔĻ one two three]</string>
  <string name="server_choice_warning">[Çûšţöm šéŕvéŕ mûšţ бé å våļîð ĥţţþš:// ÛŔĻ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
  <string name="excluded_apps">[Éxçļûðéð åþþš one two]</string>
  <string name="excluded_apps_summary">[ÐÑŠ qûéŕîéš ƒŕöm åñý šéļéçţéð åþþš ŵîļļ ñöţ ĝö ţĥŕöûĝĥ Îñţŕå.  Îƒ åñ åþþ åþþéåŕš ţö бé
    îñçömþåţîбļé ŵîţĥ Îñţŕå, ýöû çåñ åðð îţ ĥéŕé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone]</string>
  <string name="excluded_apps_title">[Måŕķ åþþš ţö éxçļûðé ƒŕöm Îñţŕå one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="old_android">[Ţĥîš ƒûñçţîöñåļîţý îš ñöţ åvåîļåбļé öñ ýöûŕ véŕšîöñ öƒ Åñðŕöîð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
  <string name="notification_title">[ÐÑŠ þŕöţéçţîöñ îš åçţîvé one two three four five]</string>
  <string name="notification_content">[Ţåþ ţö çĥåñĝé ÐÑŠ þŕöţéçţîöñ šéţţîñĝ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
  <string name="channel_name">[ÐÑŠ Þŕöţéçţîöñ Åçţîvé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñ one two three four five six seven]</string>
  <string name="channel_description">[Ţĥîš ñöţîƒîçåţîöñ åþþéåŕš ŵĥîļé ÐÑŠ þŕöţéçţîöñ îš åçţîvé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
  <string name="warning_title">[Ŵåŕñîñĝ: Îñţŕå ĥåš бééñ ðéåçţîvåţéð one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
  <string name="warning_channel_name">[Ŵåŕñîñĝ one]</string>
  <string name="warning_channel_description">[Šĥöŵñ ŵĥéñ Îñţŕå ĥåš éñçöûñţéŕéð å þŕöбļém. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
</resources>
